Guide to the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932 -1950
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1932-1950
- Series VI. 1943-1947
  - Tm - Tz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Trousdale, J.B., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - T.B. Committee, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Turk, K.L., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Turkey Disease Research Program, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Ucko, Peter W., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - U.S. Livestock Sanitary Association, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Public Health Service, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - V. Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Van Auken, G.L., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Veterinary Medical Society Prize, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Veterinarians Wanted, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Vincent, Elizabeth Lee, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Visitors, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Vivisection, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Wa - Wd, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Way, Cassius, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - We - Wh, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Weatherlow, H.E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Wegner, E.E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - West, Ralph L., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Wheeler, R.H., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Whitlock, J.H., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Wi, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Wight A.E., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Will Corporation, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Williams, H.H., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, L.A., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Wo - Wz, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - XYZ Misc., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Zeissig, Alexander, ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Zepp, C.P., ca. 1943 - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Series VII. 1947-1950
  - Aa - Al, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Accredited Herd Examination, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Addresses, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - A.G.F.U., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Agriculture, College of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Alabama Polytechnic Institute, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Allied Laboratories, Inc., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Alpha Psi, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Alpha Sigma Phi, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Office, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Am - Ar, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - American Association of University Professors, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - American Council on Education, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Anatomy, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Announcements, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Archives, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Artificial Insemination, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - As - Az, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Association of American Veterinary Deans, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - A.V.M.A. (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - A.V.M.A. (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - A.V.M.A. Council on Education, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - A.V.M.A. Women's Auxiliary, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Ba - Bo, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Bacteriology, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Baker, D.W., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Bang's Disease, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Bergey's Manual, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Borden Company Foundation, Inc., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Bra - Bz, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Youth Forum, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Youth Forum News Clippings, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Budget, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Building and Grounds, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bureau of Animal Industry, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - C, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - California, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Letter, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Letters - Full Set, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Civil Service, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Colorado A.&M., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Commencement, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Committees, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Class Advisors, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Animal Health, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Curriculum, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Student Conduct, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Complaints, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Conference, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Conferences 1948, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Conference 1949, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Rooms for Conference, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Conference of Research Workers- Animal Diseases in North America, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Veterinarian, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Country Agents, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Council for N.Y.S. Vet. College, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Council for N.Y.S.V.C., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - D, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Danforth Foundation, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Dr. G. Danks, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Data, N.Y.S. Veterinary College, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Day, Edmund Ezra, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Deans' Conferences, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Deceased - 1949 Christmas Letter, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Deceased, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - De Camp, C.E., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Diagnostic Laboratory, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Diagnostic Procedures and Reagents, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Diseases, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Dogs, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Dogs for Defense, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Dukes, H.H., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - E, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Employment, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Equipment, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Ethics, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Examinations, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Executive Committee Board of Trustees, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Expense Account - A.V.M.A., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Expense Account - N.Y.S., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Experiment Station, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - F, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Faculty, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Farm Practice, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Films, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Foot and Mouth Disease, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Inquiries, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Veterinary Schools, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - G, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Gannett Farm Letters, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Gerogia, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Goss, L.J., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - H, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Hamilton Foundation, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Hagan, W.A., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Hagan, W.A. (Trips), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Holidays, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Home Economics, College of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Honor Day, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Horses and Horse Shoeing, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Housing, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Hurt, L.M., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Hutt, F.B., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Hyperkeratosis - X Disease, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - I, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Illinois, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Inside Cornell, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - International Veterinary Congress, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Invitations, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - J, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Jennings, William E., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Jensen-Salsbery Labs, Inc., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Johne's Disease, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Juniors, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Jurisprudence, Ethics and Business Practice, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - K, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Kansas State College, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Kent, L.C., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Kentucky, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Kiesel, George K., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Klussendorf, R.C., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - L, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Laboratory, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Laboratory (Mastitis), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Laboratory - Poultry, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Land Grant Colleges, Association of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Lederle Laboratories, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Legislation, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Leonard, H.B., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - P.P. Levine, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Loans, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Long Island Duck Growers, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Libraries, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Ma - Mc, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Mastitis Program, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Me - Mx, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Medicine Department, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Medicine - Inquiries Regarding, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Merck and Co., Inc., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Merry, A.E., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Michigan State College, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Middlesex University, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Military Affairs (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Military Affairs (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Minnesota, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Minutes of Meetings, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Missouri, University of, Columbia, Mo., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Moore, E.V., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Myers, W.I., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - N, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - National Research Council, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - National Society for Medical Research, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - N.Y.S. Agricultural Society, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - N.Y.S. Conference Board of Farm Organisations, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - N.Y.S. Department of Agriculture and Markets, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - N.Y.S. Education Department, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - N.Y.S. Farm Bureau Federation, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - N.Y.S. Food Commission, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - N.Y.S. Health Department, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - N.Y. Zoological Society, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Norden Laboratories, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - North American Veterinarian, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - North Carolina, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - O, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Ohio State University, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Oklahoma A & M College, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Peter Olafson, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - P, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Papers, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Papers - "Virus Diseases and Immunity", ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Parasitology, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Pathology, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Physiology, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Position Wanted, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Prizes, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Publications, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Publicity, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Q, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - R, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Rabies, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Research, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Research and Development Board, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Reservations, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Resignations, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - S, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sao Paulo, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Schroeder, E.F., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of University, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Seniors for 1947, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Seniors 1950, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Seniors 1951, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Sherman, J.M., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Small Animal Clinic, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Summer Session, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Sunderville, E.S., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Simms, B.T., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Special Scholarship Committee, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - State Boards, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - State Food Commission, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - State University, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Stoddard, Geo D., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Student Representatives, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Surgery, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Swine, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Syracuse University Medical Center, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - T, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Telegrams, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Texas A & M College, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Traffic Control, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Tuskegee Institute, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Typhus Control, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Udall, D.H., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Public Health Service, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - University Faculty, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Vetrinaria, A.G. (Schnorf), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Veterinarian Wanted (Folder 1 of 2), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Veterinarian Wanted (Folder 2 of 2), ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Veterinarians Wanted - Old Letters, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - "Veterinary Medecine", ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Virus Research Institute, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Visitors, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Visitors - W.L. Weipers, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - W, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Washington, State College of Pullman, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Weatherlow, H.B., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Wheeler, R.H., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Williams, H.H., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Wisconsin, University of, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Youth Hostels, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Engueda Yohannes Memorial, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Zeissig, Alexander, ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Zepp, C.P., ca. 1947 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 54)